http://www.christophercook.co.uk/privacy-policy

Contact Us
Privacy PolicyChristopher Cook Designs Limited understands that your privacy is important to you and that you care about how your personal data is used. We respect and value the privacy of everyone who visits this website, christophercook.co.uk. Our Site and will only collect and use personal data in ways that are described here, and in a way that is consistent with our obligations and your rights under the law.Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and ensure that you understand it. Your acceptance of this Privacy Policy is deemed to occur upon your first use of Our Site and You will be required to read and accept this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept and agree with this Privacy Policy, you must stop using Our Site immediately.1. Definitions and InterpretationIn this Policy the following terms shall have the following meanings:  “Account”means an account required to access and/or use certain areas and features of Our Site;“Cookie”means a small text file placed on your computer or device by Our Site when you visit certain parts of Our Site and/or when you use certain features of Our Site. Details of the Cookies used by Our Site are set out in Part 14, below; and“Cookie Law”means the relevant parts of the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003;2. Information About UsOur Site is owned and operated by Christopher Cook Designs Limited, a Limited Company registered in England under company number 2295951Registered address: 29-33 Creek Road, Hampton Court, East Molesey, Surrey. KT8 9BEVAT number: 493 7097 05Data Protection Officer: Christopher BryantEmail address: contact@christophercook.co.ukTelephone number: 020 8941 9135Postal Address: 29-33 Creek Road, Hampton Court, East Molesey, Surrey. KT8 9BE 3. What Does This Policy Cover?This Privacy Policy applies only to your use of Our Site. Our Site may contain links to other websites. Please note that we have no control over how your data is collected, stored, or used by other websites and we advise you to check the privacy policies of any such websites before providing any data to them. 4. What is Personal Data?Personal data is defined by the General Data Protection Regulation (EU Regulation 2016/679) (the “GDPR”) as ‘any information relating to an identifiable person who can be directly or indirectly identified in particular by reference to an identifier’.Personal data is, in simpler terms, any information about you that enables you to be identified. Personal data covers obvious information such as your name and contact details, but it also covers less obvious information such as identification numbers, electronic location data, and other online identifiers.5. What Are My Rights?Under the GDPR, you have the following rights, which we will always work to uphold:a) The right to be informed about our collection and use of your personal data. This Privacy Policy should tell you everything you need to know, but you can always contact us to find out more or to ask any questions using the details in Part 15.b) The right to access the personal data we hold about you. Part 13 will tell you how to do this.c) The right to have your personal data rectified if any of your personal data held by us is inaccurate or incomplete. Please contact ususing the details in Part 15 to find out more.d) The right to be forgotten, i.e. the right to ask us to delete or otherwise dispose of any of your personal data that we have. Please contact us using the details in Part 15 to find out more.e) The right to restrict (i.e. prevent) the processing of your personal data.f)  The right to object to us using your personal data for a particular purpose or purposes.g) The right to data portability. This means that, if you have provided personal data to us directly, we are using it with your consent or for the performance of a contract, and that data is processed using automated means, you can ask us for a copy of that personal data to re-use with another service or business in many cases.h) Rights relating to automated decision-making and profiling. We do not use your personal data in this way.For more information about our use of your personal data or exercising your rights as outlined above, please contact ususing the details provided in Part 15.Further information about your rights can also be obtained from the Information Commissioner’s Office or your local Citizens Advice Bureau.If you have any cause for complaint about our use of your personal data, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office. 6. What Data Do We Collect?Depending upon your use of our Site, we may collect some or all of the following personal [and non-personal] data (please also see Part 14 on our use of Cookies and similar technologies and our Cookie Policy NameGenderAddressEmail addressTelephone numberBusiness nameJob titleProfessionInformation about your preferences and interestsIP addressWeb browser type and versionOperating systemA list of URLs starting with a referring site, your activity on our site, and the site you exit to 7. How Do You Use My Personal Data?Under the GDPR, we must always have a lawful basis for using personal data. This may be because the data is necessary for our performance of a contract with you, because you have consented to our use of your personal data, or because it is in our legitimate business interests to use it. Your personal data will be used for one of the following purposes:Providing and managing your Account;Providing and managing your access to our Site;[Personalising and tailoring your experience on Our Site;]Supplying products and services to you. Your personal details are required in order for us to enter into a contract with you.Personalising and tailoring our products and services for you.Communicating with you. This may include responding to emails or calls from you.Supplying you with information by email AND/OR post that you have opted-in to (you may unsubscribe or opt-out at any time by clicking the unsubscribe button on any email marketing emails).Analysing your use of Our Site and gathering feedback to enable us to continually improve Our Site and your user experience. 8. How Long Will You Keep My Personal Data?We will not keep your personal data for any longer than is necessary in light of the reason(s) for which it was first collected.9. How and Where Do You Store or Transfer My Personal Data?We will only store or transfer your personal data in the UK. This means that it will be fully protected under the GDPR. 10. Do You Share My Personal Data?We will not share any of your personal data with any third parties for any purposes, subject to one important exception.In some limited circumstances, we may be legally required to share certain personal data, which might include yours, if we are involved in legal proceedings or complying with legal obligations, a court order, or the instructions of a government authority.If any of your personal data is required by a third party, as described above, we will take steps to ensure that your personal data is handled safely, securely, and in accordance with your rights, Our obligations, and the third party’s obligations under the law, as described above in Part 9.If any personal data is transferred outside of the EEA, we will take suitable steps in order to ensure that your personal data is treated just as safely and securely as it would be within the UK and under the GDPR, as explained above in Part 9.In some limited circumstances, we may be legally required to share certain personal data, which might include yours, if we areinvolved in legal proceedings or complying with legal obligations, a court order, or the instructions of a government authority.11. How Can I Control My Personal Data?11.1 - In addition to your rights under the GDPR, set out in Part 5, whenyou submit personal data via our Site, you may be given options to restrict our use of your personal data. In particular, we aim to give you strong controls on our use of your data for direct marketing purposes (including the ability to opt-out of receiving emails from us which you may do by unsubscribing using the links provided in our emailsand, at the point of providing your details and by managing your Account).11.2 - You may also wish to sign up to one or more of the preference services operating in the UK: The Telephone Preference Service (“the TPS”), the Corporate Telephone Preference Service (“the CTPS”), and the Mailing Preference Service (“the MPS”). These may help to prevent you receiving unsolicited marketing. Please note, however, that these services willnot prevent you from receiving marketing communications that you have consented to receiving.12. Can I Withhold Information?You may access certain areas of Our Site without providing any personal data at all. However, to use all features and functions available on Our Site you may be required to submit or allow for the collection of certain data. 13. How Can I Access My Personal Data?If you want to know what personal data we have about you, you can ask us for details of that personal data and for a copy of it (where any such personal data is held). This is known as a “subject access request”.All subject access requests should be made in writing and sent to the email or postal addresses shown in Part 15. To make this as easy as possible for you, a Subject Access Request Form is available for you to use. You do not have to use this form, but it is the easiest way to tell us everything we need to know to respond to your request as quickly as possible.There is not normally any charge for a subject access request. If your request is ‘manifestly unfounded or excessive’ (for example, if you make repetitive requests) a fee may be charged to cover our administrative costs in responding.we will respond to your subject access request within 28 days and, in any case, not more than one month of receiving it. Normally, we aim to provide a complete response, including a copy of your personal data within that time. In some cases, however, particularly if your request is more complex, more time may be required up to a maximum of three months from the date we receive your request. You will be kept fully informed of our progress. Our Site uses analytics services provided by Google, Bing, Lead Forensics, HotJar. Website analytics refers to a set of tools used to collect and analyse anonymous usage information, enabling us to better understand how Our Site is used. This, in turn, enables us to improve our Site and the products and services offered through it.The analytics service(s) used by our Site use(s) Cookies to gather the required information. You do not have to allow us to use these Cookies, however whilst our use of them does not pose any risk to your privacy or your safe use of our Site, it does enable us to continually improve our Site, making it a better and more useful experience for you.The analytics service(s) used by our site use(s) the following Cookies: Name of CookieFirst / Third PartyProviderPurpose_gaThirdGoogleAnalytics Tracking_gatThirdGoogleAnalytics Tracking_gidThirdGoogleAnalytics TrackingOur Site may place and access certain first-party Cookies on your computer or device. First-party Cookies are those placed directly by us and are used only by us. We use Cookies to facilitate and improve your experience of our site and to provide and improve our products and services. By using our site you may also receive certain third-party Cookies on your computer or device. Third-party Cookies are those placed by websites, services, and/or parties other than us. Third-party Cookies are used on Our Site for tracking analytics of our users. In addition, our site uses analytics services provided by Google, HotJar, Bing, Lead Forensics, which also use Cookies. Website analytics refers to a set of tools used to collect and analyse usage statistics, enabling us to better understand how people use Our Site. For more details, please refer to our Cookie Policy 15. How Do I Contact You?To contact us about anything to do with your personal data and data protection, including to make a subject access request, please use the following:Email address: contact@christophercook.co.ukTelephone number: 020 8941 9135Postal Address: 29-33 Creek Road, Hampton Court, East Molesey, Surrey. KT8 9BE 16. Changes to this Privacy PolicyWe may change this Privacy Notice from time to time. This may be necessary, for example, if the law changes, or if we change our business in a way that affects personal data protection.Any changes will be immediately posted on Our Site and you will be deemed to have accepted the terms of the Privacy Policy on your first use of Our Site following the alterations. We recommend that you check this page regularly to keep up-to-date. We are always looking to improve our website, your comments good or bad are gladly welcome
"our team CREATEs ALL styles OF INTERIORS FROM THE MOST ELABORATE warm TRADITIONAL TO the more STRIKING cool CONTEMPORARY."Copyright © 2016 Christopher Cook Designs Ltd. All rights reserved.
